# CHETAN SINDHE

Front End UI Specialist



+(91)974-076-6266

csindhe@gmail.com

**44** 06-Aug-1985

Bengaluru

#### **About Me**

An avid programmer with prolific knowledge on Angular & Javascript possessing pragmatic approach to the real-time problems or requirements. Have been an active player in the innovtion design and implementation with a flair for generating new ideas based on the current project scenarios. Also a quick learner of new skills with an eve for constant evolution in knowledge and continous improvement towards the technical expertise thus becoming a strong player in the design and implementation.

## **Primary Skills**

| Angular                    | **** |
|----------------------------|------|
| REACT JS                   | ***  |
| JAVASCRIPT                 | **** |
| Typescript/ES6             | **** |
| RXJS OBSERVABLES           | **** |
| REDUX                      | **** |
| BACKBONE JS                | ***  |
| JAVASCRIPT DESIGN PATTERNS | **** |

## **Secondary Skills**

HTML, CSS, JQUERY

JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT

Angular (4+), Angular + Redux

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

#### **Education**

**B.E Mechanical Engineering** 

## **Work Experience**

## **UI PROGRAMMER / CONSULTANT**

Infosys Ltd.

Nov 2017 - Present



10 Years 6 Months

Was involved in UI/Ux development for the Web as part of Packaged application for Cloudcraze. Used Javascript, Html, CSS, Jquery and BackboneJS for implementing requirements. Created an opportunity to explore Angular 4.0/5.0, Redux more under Infosys's IPR initiative for new ideas. Was actively involved in building a Cafeteria App as a side project (for ordering food online in order to reduce queue at each kiosk) in our spare time.

#### TECH LEAD / UI PROGRAMMER

Tech Mahindra Ltd.

July 2015 - Oct 2017

Tech Mahindra

Actively involved in Innovative Idea Initiative for User Interface for Telia Company. As part of the initiative I used BackboneJS, ReactJS, Angular 2.0/4.0, RxJS and Responsive Web UI over the course of 2 years in order to develop Order Management (ReactJS) and Service Management applications (Angular).

#### TEAM LEAD / UI PROGRAMMER

Cognizant Ltd.

Oct 2007 - June 2015



Worked in following technologies like Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS as part of project requirements. Have also worked on packaged solution like Siebel CRM in Healthcare, ePharma and Telecom. Was instrumental in developing intuitive UI under Siebel OpenUI (Facade pattern) umbrella (OneView Dashboard).